LAWAL ZAYNAB

Teacher's Estate Ilefon Ijebu ode, Ogun state Phone: 08135067216 E-mail: holamideh8@gmail.com

OBJECTIVES

A research enthusiast, willing to learn and broaden my horizon, capable of functioning effectively as an entity and as a team, navigating through the proliferating world of technology. I seek a role to leverage technical expertise and excellence.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE in Biochemistry

(2019-2022)

Olabisi Onabanjo University

Cgpa: 3.19/5.0

Thesis on: Changes in blood glucose level overtime after consuming certain Nigerian.

ORDINARY NATIONAL DIPLOMA in Science Laboratory Technology

(2016-2018)

Abraham Adesanya Polytechnic

Upper credit

Thesis on: Bioplastics degradation and its effects in the ecosystem.

Ad dawah Comprehensive College, Ijebu ode, Ogun state.

(2009-2015)

Senior Secondary Certificate Examination

Ad dawah Nursery and Primary School, Ijebu Ode, Ogun State.

(2000-2009)

First School Leaving Certificate

WORK EXPERIENCE

NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS, OYO STATE.

(NOV 2023 -OCT 2024)

Islamic Boys High School (Iseyin, Oyo State)

Chemistry Teacher

- Communication skills, which involves conveying complex information clearly.
- Leadership and management of classroom.
- Planning and executing programs at stipulated time.

.....

GOD'S KNOT HOSPITAL AND FERTILITY CENTER IBADAN OYO STATE (AUG2022-SEPT2022 2022)

- Laboratory research which involves the use of high functioning apparatus.
- Sensory evaluation, scientific discipline which encompasses all methods to analyze and interprete human response to properties of food and materials.
- Efficient and effective team work which led to the success of all experiment.

OYO STATE PRIMARY HEALTH CARE BOARD

(JAN 2022- JUN2022)

- Participated in a coordinated dispensation of COVID 19 vaccines.
- Data analysis, doses of vaccines taken were computed correctly on the system.
- Collaborated with functional teams, enhancing project success rates

SKILLS

- Strong analytical and problem solving abilities.
- Excellent communication and presentation skills.
- Project management and organization skills.
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- Time management and multitasking capability.
- Data analysis and statistical software(SPSS).

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCES

SDGs CDS President, NYSC Iseyin.

- Participated in community outreach programs focused on Sustainable Development Goals(SDGs)
- Educated community members about sustainable practices and initiatives.
- Collaborated with local organization to implement community improvement projects.